Personal info Tang Wei Xun (Matthew)

- Pedok North Avenue 3, 460403 Bedok, Singapore
- **** 87683698
- matth3w_wx@hotmail.com
- Singapore Citizen
- 26/09/1991

Profile

About Myself

A Self-Motivated Individual, with 3 years of experience in software development. Always excited to deeper my knowledge to undertake any challenges

Skills

Development Skills Software Skills Java **JIRA 0000** Confluence Spring 0000 0000 SOL **Eclipse** Hibernate **GIT** 0000 0000 Angular 7 0000 Maven 0000

Development Methodologies

Agile	••000
Waterfall	••000

Work experience

07/2018 - present

Software Developer Associate

Accenture, Singapore

- Contribute software engineering expertise in the development of products
- Leverage on spring framework to develop, test, implement and maintain application to perform various tasks for its clients. (Spring-Batch)
- Developed program in maven, program structure and dependencies.
- Wrote unit test, for each built class. Utilizing jacoco to ensure coverage
- Applied relevant technical skills, to deliver specification, program changes.
- · Assist in deploying of codes. From one environment to another.
- Build front-end UI, with angular 7.

08/2016 - 06/2018

Software Engineer New Associate

Accenture, Singapore

- Assisted in development of user requirements, for the clients of Accenture.
- Leverage on spring framework to develop, test, implement and maintain application to perform various tasks for its clients.
- Conduct live demonstration of the build applications, to the clients of Accenture.
- Wrote native SQL queries in the program, executed via JDBC template to perform database operation.
- Invoke docu-sign rest API, to implement signing of documents.

04/2015 - 08/2015

Android Developer (Internship)

ST Electronics, Singapore

Collaborate with ST Electronics for requirements & translate into specifications for development team.

Collaborate with supervisor for new initiatives & in charge of the overall technical solutioning.

Identify areas to improve in terms of productivity, propose, design solution, prototype & implement.

Education	
01/2016 - 01/2017	Specialist Diploma In Smart Solutions Temasek Polytechnic, Singapore
01/2014 - 01/2016	Diploma In Info-Communication Network Engineering Temasek Polytechnic, Singapore
01/2009 - 01/2010	Nitec in Info-Communications Technology. Institute of Technical Education, Singapore